[{"file_name": "Can you think of other ways of defending human dignity and sacredness, that aren't Reason?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Can you think of other ways of defending human dignity and sacredness, that aren't Reason?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Reason]]", "[[Human Dignity]]"], "question_text": "Can you think of other ways of defending human dignity and sacredness, that aren't Reason?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:34:24", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:58:24"}, {"file_name": "What causes people to stink? And could we prevent it?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/What causes people to stink? And could we prevent it?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["biology", "ecology"], "related": ["[[bacteria]]"], "question_text": "What causes people to stink? And could we prevent it?", "answer_text": "Thioalcohols, which is a product of our sweat mixing with an enzyme C-T lyase produced by the bacterium Staphylococcus hominis", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:30:34", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:54:34"}, {"file_name": "How do you convert one data type in Python to another data type? How to convert?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/How do you convert one data type in Python to another data type? How to convert?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Data type]]"], "question_text": "How do you convert one data type in Python to another data type? How to convert? list to set, str to int?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:27:40", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:51:40"}, {"file_name": "Have you ever considered how you might reach out to someone in your life to ask a favor?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Have you ever considered how you might reach out to someone in your life to ask a favor?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[artistic proofs]]"], "question_text": "Have you ever considered how you might reach out to someone in your life to ask a favor? If so how?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:31:08", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:55:08"}, {"file_name": "Given a list of numbers, how would you find the minimum and maximum values?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Given a list of numbers, how would you find the minimum and maximum values?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[list]]"], "question_text": "Given a list of numbers, how would you find the minimum and maximum values?", "answer_text": "Use either the max or min method\nExample:\nlist1 = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]\nprint(min(list1))\nprint(max(list1))", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:32:56", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:56:56"}, {"file_name": "What is the idea of Materialism?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the idea of Materialism?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Materialism]]", "[[Mathematization]]"], "question_text": "What is the idea of Materialism defined as?", "answer_text": " All things are made up of matter, physical stuff, there is no immaterial aspect to the world such as ghosts && The idea that the universe is ONLY composed of material, physical reality. Everything should be explainable as physical phenomenon.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:25:27", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:49:27"}, {"file_name": "What is the proper structure for the table element in HTML?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the proper structure for the table element in HTML?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the proper structure for the table element in HTML?", "answer_text": "<table>\n   <tr>\n    <th>Company</th>\n    <th>Contact</th>\n    <th>Country</th>\n  </tr>\n  <tr>\n    <td>Alfreds Futterkiste</td>\n    <td>Maria Anders</td>\n    <td>Germany</td>\n  </tr>\n  <tr>\n    <td>Centro comercial Moctezuma</td>\n    <td>Francisco Chang</td>\n    <td>Mexico</td>\n  </tr>\n</table>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:27:12", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:51:12"}, {"file_name": "Does a single writing process work best for every author and every writing task?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Does a single writing process work best for every author and every writing task?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["writing"], "related": ["[[Everyone's an Author - Managing the Writing Process - 9]]"], "question_text": "Does a single writing process work best for every author and every writing task?", "answer_text": "No, work instead to develop a repertoire of strategies that will enable you to become efficient, productive, and effective writer.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:30:05", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:54:05"}, {"file_name": "What is the period the sine and cosine functions?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the period the sine and cosine functions?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[sine]]", "[[cosine]]", "[[period]]"], "question_text": "What is the period of the sine and cosine functions?", "answer_text": "2\u03c0", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:26:29", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:50:29"}, {"file_name": "What is the base syntax for the form element in an html document?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the base syntax for the form element in an html document?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "What is the base syntax for the form element in an html document?", "answer_text": "<form action=\"/mailinglist.php\" method=\"POST\">\n\t<fieldset>\n\t\t<legend>Join our email list</legend>\n\t\t<p></p>\n\t\t<ol>\n\t\t\t<li><label for=\"firstlast\">Name:</label>\n\t\t\t\t<input type=\"text\" name=\"fullname\" id=\"firstlast\">\n\t\t\t</li>\n\t\t\t<li><label for=\"email\">Email:</label>\n\t\t\t\t<input type=\"text\" name=\"email\">\n\t\t\t</li>\n\t\t</ol>\n\t\t<input type=\"submit\" value=\"Submit\">\n\t</fieldset>\n</form>", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:31:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 06:31:49"}, {"file_name": "Sometimes arguments have an implicit premise. What does this mean?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Sometimes arguments have an implicit premise. What does this mean?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[premise]]"], "question_text": "Sometimes arguments have an implicit premise. What does this mean?", "answer_text": "An implicit premise is one that is not stated in an argument but is required to", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:30:43", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:54:43"}, {"file_name": "A circle has radius of 18 inches. Find the arc length and the area of corresponding to a rotation of a. 1.5 radians and b. 109\u00b0..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/A circle has radius of 18 inches. Find the arc length and the area of corresponding to a rotation of a. 1.5 radians and b. 109\u00b0.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[arclength]]", "[[radian]]", "[[area of a sector]]"], "question_text": "A circle has radius of 18 inches. Find the arc length and the area of corresponding to a rotation of a. 1.5 radians and b. 109\u00b0", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:28:56", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:52:56"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML for making a text area?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML for making a text area?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML for making a text area?", "answer_text": "<textarea> </textarea>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:27:55", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:51:55"}, {"file_name": "Given a list of numbers, how would you get the sum of the values inside the list?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Given a list of numbers, how would you get the sum of the values inside the list?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[list]]"], "question_text": "Given a list of numbers, how would you get the sum of the values inside the list?", "answer_text": "Using the sum function:\nlist_of_numbers = [1,2,3]\nsum = sum(list_of_numbers)\nprint(sum(list_of_numbers)", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:33:15", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:57:15"}, {"file_name": "Ask the user for a floating-point number. Prints the number in decimal form with 4 decimal places. Prints the number in scientific notation with 2 decimal places...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Ask the user for a floating-point number. Prints the number in decimal form with 4 decimal places. Prints the number in scientific notation with 2 decimal places..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[float]]", "[[round()]]", "[[scientific notation]]"], "question_text": "Ask the user for a floating-point number. Prints the number in decimal form with 4 decimal places. Prints the number in scientific notation with 2 decimal places.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:33:54", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:57:54"}, {"file_name": "Question 6.1.1..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Question 6.1.1.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[sine]]", "[[tangent]]", "[[negative identity]]"], "question_text": "Simplify sin(-\u03b8)/tan(\u03b8)", "answer_text": "-cos(\u03b8)", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:32:38", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:56:38"}, {"file_name": "In argument reconstruction, what is a claim? How does it differ from a premise?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In argument reconstruction, what is a claim? How does it differ from a premise?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[claim]]", "[[premise]]"], "question_text": "In argument reconstruction, what is a claim? How does it differ from a premise?", "answer_text": "A statement that can be either true or false \nA premise is a claim given as a reason in support of the truth of a conclusion.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:26:40", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:50:40"}, {"file_name": "What html form elements are used to ask for text?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What html form elements are used to ask for text?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "What html form elements are used to ask for text? What's the difference between the two?", "answer_text": "<input> and <textarea> \ninput is used for a single line of text\ntextarea is used for multiple lines of text", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:32:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:56:16"}, {"file_name": "Three ways to check on whether a story can be trusted..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Three ways to check on whether a story can be trusted.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": null, "question_text": "Name three ways to check on whether a story can be trusted.", "answer_text": "1. Google the author or the sponsor\n2. Look for other sources that are reporting the same story, especially if you first saw it on social media.\n3. Check FactCheck.org or Snopes", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:29:12", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:53:12"}, {"file_name": "Explain the five steps of Monroe's Motivated Sequence..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Explain the five steps of Monroe's Motivated Sequence.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Monroe's Motivated Sequence]]"], "question_text": "What are the five steps of Monroe's Motivated Sequence", "answer_text": "Monroe's Motivated Sequence includes five steps: \n1. attention, \n2. need, \n3. satisfaction, \n4. visualization, and \n5. action.\nANSVA", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:25:33", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:49:33"}, {"file_name": "Define Disjunctive syllogism..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Define Disjunctive syllogism.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Disjunctive syllogism]]"], "question_text": "What is the structure of a disjunctive syllogism argument?", "answer_text": "P or Q, P is not true\ntherefore Q", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:29:52", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:53:52"}, {"file_name": "What is the most effective way to give sight-impaired users an overview of your html table?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the most effective way to give sight-impaired users an overview of your html table?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]", "[[Accessibility]]"], "question_text": "What is the most effective way to give sight-impaired users an overview of your html table?", "answer_text": "Give it a title or description with the caption element\n<caption>This Is An Example</caption>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:26:02", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:50:02"}, {"file_name": "In the textarea form element, what does the cols attribute do? What is the proper syntax to use the cols attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the textarea form element, what does the cols attribute do? What is the proper syntax to use the cols attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": null, "question_text": "In the textarea form element, what does the cols attribute do? What is the proper syntax to use the cols attribute?", "answer_text": "<textarea name=\"\" cols=\"num_characters\">...</textarea>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:29:38", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:53:38"}, {"file_name": "What counter-objection does Spinoza raise against the view that mental and physical states are merely coincidental and the mind neither controls the body nor controls events in the physical world?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What counter-objection does Spinoza raise against the view that mental and physical states are merely coincidental and the mind neither controls the body nor controls events in the physical world?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Baruch Spinoza]]"], "question_text": "What counter-objection does Spinoza raise against the view that mental and physical states are merely coincidental and the mind neither controls the body nor controls events in the physical world?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:26:45", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:50:45"}, {"file_name": "What are the two types of igneous rock?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are the two types of igneous rock?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["geology"], "related": ["[[igneous rock]]"], "question_text": "What are the two types of igneous rock?", "answer_text": "1. Intrusive (Plutonic) rocks:\n2. Extrusive (Volcanic) rocks:", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:34:02", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:58:02"}, {"file_name": "Who were the anabaptists, who led this movement and when?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Who were the anabaptists, who led this movement and when?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["history", "religion"], "related": ["[[Anabaptism]]"], "question_text": "Who were the anabaptists, who led this movement and when?", "answer_text": "Anabaptism in Switzerland began as an offshoot of the church reforms instigated by Ulrich Zwingli. As early as 1522, it became evident that Zwingli was on a path of reform preaching when he began to question or criticize such Catholic practices as tithes, the mass, and even infant baptism.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:25:46", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:49:46"}, {"file_name": "Where does the phrase \"Caesar non est supra grammaticos\" orginate from?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Where does the phrase \"Caesar non est supra grammaticos\" orginate from?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["history"], "related": ["[[Frederick the Great]]"], "question_text": "Where does the phrase \"Caesar non est supra grammaticos\" orginate from?", "answer_text": "incident involving the Holy Roman Emperor Sigismund at the Council of Constance in 1414", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:35:20", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:59:20"}, {"file_name": "Define Modus tollens..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Define Modus tollens.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Modus tollens]]"], "question_text": "What is the argument pattern for a Modus Tollens argument structure?", "answer_text": "- If P then Q.- Not-Q.- Therefore, not-P.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:34:46", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:58:46"}, {"file_name": "In a program what is a branch defined as?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In a program what is a branch defined as?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[while loop]]", "[[if-else branch]]"], "question_text": "In a program what is a branch defined as?", "answer_text": "A sequence of statements only executed under a certain condition", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:31:56", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:55:56"}, {"file_name": "How to add links to a website?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How to add links to a website?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Adding Links - 6]]"], "question_text": "How to add links to a website using HTML?", "answer_text": "<a href=\"\"\" target=\"\">Some Text</a>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:35:04", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:59:04"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML element for playing video files?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML element for playing video files?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML element for playing video files?", "answer_text": "<video controls width=\"250\">  \n<source src=\"/media/cc0-videos/flower.webm\" type=\"video/webm\" /></video>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:35:56", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 08:59:56"}, {"file_name": "Channels 00-599 are pay channels Does this expression detect that range? - - -..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Channels 00-599 are pay channels Does this expression detect that range? - - -.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[logical operator]]"], "question_text": "Channels 500-599 are pay channels Does this expression detect that range? \n(user_channel >= 500) or (user_channel <= 599)", "answer_text": "No, the logical operator used is or. This expression detects all channels, not a range. The desired operator is what?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:37:57", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:01:57"}, {"file_name": "In the input form element, what does the placeholder attribute do? What is the proper syntax for the placeholder attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the input form element, what does the placeholder attribute do? What is the proper syntax for the placeholder attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In the input form element, what does the placeholder attribute do? What is the proper syntax for the placeholder attribute?", "answer_text": "<input name=\"\" type=\"textarea\" placeholder=\"default_text\">...</input>\nYou can use the placeholder attribute to provide a hint of what to type in a field. The value of placeholder is not submitted with the form, and is purely a user interface enhancement.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:42:07", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:06:07"}, {"file_name": "Is x =< y a valid expression?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Is x =< y a valid expression?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[expression]]", "[[Relational Operator]]"], "question_text": "Is x =< y a valid expression?", "answer_text": "No:\nShould be: x >= y", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:44:06", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:08:06"}, {"file_name": "What is the core premise of the idea of Rationalism?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the core premise of the idea of Rationalism?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Materialism]]", "[[Mathematization]]", "[[Rationalism]]"], "question_text": "What is the core premise of the idea of Rationalism?", "answer_text": "that opinions and actions should be based on reason and knowledge rather than on religious belief or emotional response.Foundation of knowledge is a a priori", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:37:51", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:01:51"}, {"file_name": "How to install a .deb package?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How to install a .deb package?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Linux]]"], "question_text": "How to install a .deb package?", "answer_text": "sudo dpkg -i filename.deb", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:39:19", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:03:19"}, {"file_name": "According to Spinoza, why do many persons believe human beings have free will? How can we become conscious or discover the causes of our decisions and the unconscious appetites upon which they depend?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/According to Spinoza, why do many persons believe human beings have free will? How can we become conscious or discover the causes of our decisions and the unconscious appetites upon which they depend?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Baruch Spinoza]]"], "question_text": "According to Spinoza, why do many persons believe human beings have free will? How can we become conscious or discover the causes of our decisions and the unconscious appetites upon which they depend?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:39:21", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:03:21"}, {"file_name": "What is the inequality operator? When do you use it?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the inequality operator? When do you use it?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Operator]]"], "question_text": "What is the inequality operator? When do you use it?", "answer_text": "!=", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:41:53", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:05:53"}, {"file_name": "What is the caption element used for in HTML?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the caption element used for in HTML?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]", "[[Accessibility]]"], "question_text": "What is the caption element used for in HTML?", "answer_text": "To provide a description of an html table, and to provide accessibility to a site:\n<table>\n  <caption>Nutritional Information</caption>\n  <tr>\n  <th>Menu item</th>\n  <th>Calories</th>\n  <th>Fat (g)</th>\n  </tr> <!-- table continues --> \n</table>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:45:07", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:09:07"}, {"file_name": "another name for horizontal shift is what?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/another name for horizontal shift is what?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[transformation]]"], "question_text": "Another name for a horizontal shift is what?", "answer_text": "phase shift", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:46:01", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:10:01"}, {"file_name": "You have an html form and would like to provide suggested options for an input field. How should you accomplish this?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/You have an html form and would like to provide suggested options for an input field. How should you accomplish this?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "You have an html form and would like to provide suggested options for an input field. How should you accomplish this?", "answer_text": "Using the datalist element", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:47:15", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:11:15"}, {"file_name": "What is the equality operator? When do you use it?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the equality operator? When do you use it?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Operator]]", "[[branch]]"], "question_text": "What is the equality operator? When do you use it?", "answer_text": "==", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:45:57", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:09:57"}, {"file_name": "When creating a table in html, how do you describe rows or groups of rows as belonging to header, footer or the body of a table?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When creating a table in html, how do you describe rows or groups of rows as belonging to header, footer or the body of a table?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "When creating a table in html, how do you describe rows or groups of rows as belonging to header, footer or the body of a table?", "answer_text": "By using the <thead></thead>, <tbody></tbody>, and <tfoot></tfoot> elements", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:43:06", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 06:43:06"}, {"file_name": "True or False, An <iframe> is used to. . ...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/True or False, An <iframe> is used to. . ..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "True or False. An <iframe> is used to display a web page within a web page.", "answer_text": "True", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:40:08", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:04:08"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML element to define important text?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML element to define important text?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML element to define important text?", "answer_text": "<strong>important</strong>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:42:17", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:06:17"}, {"file_name": "In an HTML form, what does the term \"form controls\" refer to?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In an HTML form, what does the term \"form controls\" refer to?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In an HTML form, what does the term \"form controls\" refer to?", "answer_text": "Forms are made up of buttons, input fields, and drop-down menus (collectively known as form controls)", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:40:41", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:04:41"}, {"file_name": "What is the Cosine of?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the Cosine of?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[cosine]]"], "question_text": "What is the cosine of the following:\n0 - pi/6 - pi/4 - pi/3 - pi/2 - 2pi/3 - 3pi/4 - 5pi/6 - pi", "answer_text": "0 = 1\npi/6 = sqrt(3)/2\npi/4 = sqrt(2)/2\npi/3 = 1/2\npi/2 = 0\n2pi/3 = -1/2\n3pi/4 = -sqrt(2)/2\n5pi/6 = -sqrt(3)/2\npi = -1", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:40:04", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:04:04"}, {"file_name": "Any problems with thinking it's reason that makes humans valuable?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Any problems with thinking it's reason that makes humans valuable?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Reason]]", "[[Human Dignity]]"], "question_text": "Any problems with thinking it's reason that makes humans valuable?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:44:41", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:08:41"}, {"file_name": "Why does misinformation outperform real news?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Why does misinformation outperform real news?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication", "writing"], "related": ["[[misinformation effect]]", "[[cause-and-effect]]"], "question_text": "Why does misinformation outperform real news?", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:41:26", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:05:26"}, {"file_name": "Who is making the Web standards?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Who is making the Web standards?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[World Wide Web]]"], "question_text": "Who is making the Web standards?", "answer_text": "The World Wide Web Consortium (W3C)", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:44:44", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:08:44"}, {"file_name": "Examine the following html001, what is the result?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Examine the following html001, what is the result?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "Examine the following html, what is the result? \n<p><label>Official contest entry: <br>\n<em>Tell us why you love the band. Fiver winners will get backstage \npasses!</em><br>\n<textarea name=\"contest_entry\" rows=\"5\" cols=\"50\"> The band is totally awesome!</textarea></label></p>", "answer_text": "The text \"The band is totally awesome!\" will be inserted into the textarea on the webpage. The rest of the text will be outside of the text area above it.\nThe text area will be 5 rows long and 50 characters wide", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:44:03", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:08:03"}, {"file_name": "The result of evaluating nums - slice notation1..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/The result of evaluating nums - slice notation1.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Python]]", "[[slice notation]]"], "question_text": "Given the following code:\nnums = [0, 25, 50, 75, 100]\nThe result of evaluating nums[0:5:2] is [25,75]: True or False\nThe result of evaluating nums[0:-1:3] is [0,75]: True or False", "answer_text": "False \nTrue", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:38:19", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:02:19"}, {"file_name": "Which HTML element defines the title of a document?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Which HTML element defines the title of a document?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "Which HTML element defines the title of a document? Where is it placed in the HTML?", "answer_text": "<head>\n <title> </title>\n</head>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:37:15", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:01:15"}, {"file_name": "question on the spirit of modernity..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/question on the spirit of modernity.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[scientific revolution]]", "[[The Age of Reason]]", "[[Autonomy]]", "[[freedom]]", "[[Mathematization]]"], "question_text": "The \u201cspirit of modernity\u201d or the \u201cstory of modernity.\u201d These phrases are used for the idea of a basic shift in thinking that we characterize as modernity. So far, what are some features of \u201cmodern thinking\u201d? How does it diRer from what came before?", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:43:38", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:07:38"}, {"file_name": "What form control elements are required to allow the user to either clear the form or submit it to the server?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What form control elements are required to allow the user to either clear the form or submit it to the server?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "What form control elements are required to allow the user to either clear the form or submit it to the server? Provide the correct html syntax for both these elements contained within a paragraph element.", "answer_text": "<p><input type=\"submit\" value=\"defaults_to_submit\"><input type=\"reset\" value=\"defaults_to_reset\"></p>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:44:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:08:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the negative identity of cosine?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the negative identity of cosine?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[cosine]]"], "question_text": "What is the negative identity of cosine?", "answer_text": "$$cos(-\\theta) = cos(\\theta)$$", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:44:53", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:08:53"}, {"file_name": "What is the scope attribute in an HTML table do?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the scope attribute in an HTML table do?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": null, "question_text": "What is the scope attribute in an HTML table do?", "answer_text": "The scope attribute associates a table header with the row, column, group of rows (such tbody), or column group in which it appears.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:36:42", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:00:42"}, {"file_name": "Which HTML attribute specifies an alternate text for an image, if the image cannot be displayed?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Which HTML attribute specifies an alternate text for an image, if the image cannot be displayed?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "Which HTML attribute specifies an alternate text for an image, if the image cannot be displayed?", "answer_text": "alt=\"displayed text\"", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:39:03", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:03:03"}, {"file_name": "When using the pop method on list, which index number is removed?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When using the pop method on list, which index number is removed?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[pop()]]"], "question_text": "When using the pop method on list, if no value is specified in pop(), which index number is removed?", "answer_text": "The last index is removed if no value is specified", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:45:23", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:09:23"}, {"file_name": "What is the unicode character for infinity?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the unicode character for infinity?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Linux]]", "[[Unicode hexidecimal table]]"], "question_text": "What is the unicode character for infinity?", "answer_text": "U+221E = \u221e", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 06:41:05", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 09:05:05"}, {"file_name": "How have socializing agents shaped the way you communicate?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How have socializing agents shaped the way you communicate?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[socializing agents]]"], "question_text": "How have socializing agents shaped the way you communicate?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:19:50", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:43:50"}, {"file_name": "Given a list, how do you reverse the order of the list?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Given a list, how do you reverse the order of the list?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[list]]"], "question_text": "Given a list, how do you reverse the order of the list?", "answer_text": "To reverse the order of a list use the reverse method:\nExample:\ncharacters = [\"a\",\"b\",\"c\",\"d\"]\ncharacters.reverse()", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:05:43", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:29:43"}, {"file_name": "In argument reconstruction, what is a Conclusion defined as?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In argument reconstruction, what is a Conclusion defined as?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Conclusion]]"], "question_text": "In argument reconstruction, what is a Conclusion defined as?", "answer_text": "The main claim one is attempting to prove is True", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:21:39", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:45:39"}, {"file_name": "In visual browsers, the arrangement of data in rows and columns gives readers what advantage?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In visual browsers, the arrangement of data in rows and columns gives readers what advantage?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "In visual browsers, the arrangement of data in rows and columns gives readers what advantage?", "answer_text": "An instant understanding of the relationships between data cells and their respective header labels", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:25:04", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:49:04"}, {"file_name": "This is test note 1..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/This is test note 1.md", "type": "question", "subject": null, "related": null, "question_text": "this is a test note", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:20:01", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:44:01"}, {"file_name": "What does the colgroup element do?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What does the colgroup element do?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "What does the colgroup element do? What content do they contain?", "answer_text": "Semantically groups columns, they do not contain any content- they only provide an indication of semantically relevant column structure.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:05:10", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:29:10"}, {"file_name": "Inline Elements are normally displayed without starting a new line? T or F..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Inline Elements are normally displayed without starting a new line? T or F.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "True or False? Inline Elements are normally displayed without starting a new line?", "answer_text": "True", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:17:26", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:41:26"}, {"file_name": "In the input form element, what does the size attribute do? What is the proper syntax for the size attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the input form element, what does the size attribute do? What is the proper syntax for the size attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In the input form element, what does the size attribute do? What is the proper syntax for the size attribute?", "answer_text": "The size attribute specifies the length of the input field in number of visible characters. It is more common, however, to use style sheets to set the size of the input area.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:10:33", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:34:33"}, {"file_name": "What is the proper html markdown to use the thead, tfoot, and tbody elements?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the proper html markdown to use the thead, tfoot, and tbody elements?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "What is the proper html markdown to use the thead, tfoot, and tbody elements?", "answer_text": "<table>\n<thead><tr><tr><tr></thead>\n<tbody><tr><tr><tr></tbody>\n<tfoot><tr><tr><tr></tfoot>\n</table>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:08:00", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:32:00"}, {"file_name": "True or False, block elements . . ...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/True or False, block elements . . ..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "True or False? Block elements are normally displayed without starting a new line.", "answer_text": "False, block elements always start on a new line", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:17:34", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:41:34"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML for making a drop-down list?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML for making a drop-down list?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML for making a drop-down list?", "answer_text": "<select name=\"pets\" id=\"pet-select\">\n  <option value=\"\">--Please choose an option--</option>\n  <option value=\"dog\">Dog</option>\n  <option value=\"cat\">Cat</option>\n  <option value=\"hamster\">Hamster</option>\n  <option value=\"parrot\">Parrot</option>\n  <option value=\"spider\">Spider</option>\n  <option value=\"goldfish\">Goldfish</option>\n</select>", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:14:30", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 12:14:30"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML for making a text input field?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML for making a text input field?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML for making a text input field?", "answer_text": "<input type=\"text\">", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:05:28", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:29:28"}, {"file_name": "There are two parts to a working form on a website, what are these two parts?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/There are two parts to a working form on a website, what are these two parts?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": null, "question_text": "There are two parts to a working form on a website, what are these two parts?", "answer_text": "1. The part that you see on the page itself, the buttons, input fields, and drop-down menus. \n2. The application or script on the server that processes the information collected by the form and returns an appropriate response.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:07:08", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:31:08"}, {"file_name": "how do you assign a variable with a boolean data type?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/how do you assign a variable with a boolean data type?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[boolean]]", "[[assignment statement]]"], "question_text": "how do you assign a variable with a boolean data type?", "answer_text": "my_bool = True\nOR\nmy_bool = False\nOR with an expression:\nis_small = my_val < 3", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:15:13", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:39:13"}, {"file_name": "Who is the Roman God of Fire?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Who is the Roman God of Fire?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mythology"], "related": ["[[Vulcan]]"], "question_text": "Who is the Roman God of Fire?", "answer_text": "Vulcan", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:16:07", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:40:07"}, {"file_name": "What are Kant's reasons for supporting Intellectual Freedom?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are Kant's reasons for supporting Intellectual Freedom?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Immanuel Kant]]", "[[freedom]]"], "question_text": "What are Kant's reasons for supporting Intellectual Freedom?", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:09:07", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:33:07"}, {"file_name": "In slice notation, what happens if you enter a negative value for the slice stride argument?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In slice notation, what happens if you enter a negative value for the slice stride argument?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[slice notation]]"], "question_text": "In slice notation, what happens if you enter a negative value for the slice stride argument?\nExample: my_str[::-X]", "answer_text": "reverses the order of the list, with X being the step. if x is 2 then every other going in reverse order, if x is 3 then every third going in reverse order", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:15:51", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:39:51"}, {"file_name": "How do you make a bulleted list in an HTML document?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How do you make a bulleted list in an HTML document?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "How do you make a bulleted list in an HTML document?", "answer_text": "<ul>\n<li></li>\n<li></li>\n</ul>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:21:59", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:45:59"}, {"file_name": "You have an html form and would like to restrict the user input to specified list of options, how do you do this? Provide the proper syntax for the required method...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/You have an html form and would like to restrict the user input to specified list of options, how do you do this? Provide the proper syntax for the required method..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "You have an html form and would like to restrict the user input to specified list of options, how do you do this? Provide the proper syntax for the required method.", "answer_text": "Use the select element\n<p> Add some text here:\n<select name=\"\">\n   <option>opt1</option>\n   <option value=\"Optional value entry, won't be seen by user:\">opt2</option>\n   <option>opt3</option>\n</select></p>\n\nThe result is menu that is inside of an inline element, the select element is an inline element.", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:26:10", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 12:26:10"}, {"file_name": "What does HTML stand for?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What does HTML stand for?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What does HTML stand for?", "answer_text": "HyperText Markup Language", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:11:30", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:35:30"}, {"file_name": "In the HTML form element, what does the method attribute default to?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the HTML form element, what does the method attribute default to?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In the HTML form element, what does the method attribute default to if omitted?", "answer_text": "The method is optional and will default to GET if omitted.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:24:32", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:48:32"}, {"file_name": "What is the range of sine and cosine is the interval?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the range of sine and cosine is the interval?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[sine]]", "[[cosine]]", "[[range]]"], "question_text": "What is the range of sine and cosine, in interval notation?", "answer_text": "[-1, 1]", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:16:02", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:40:02"}, {"file_name": "Are there really such universals? If so, what is their nature? How are they related to individuals?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Are there really such universals? If so, what is their nature? How are they related to individuals?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[universals]]", "[[Universalism]]"], "question_text": "Are there really such universals? If so, what is their nature? How are they related to individuals?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:09:47", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:33:47"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML element for playing audio files?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML element for playing audio files?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML element for playing audio files?", "answer_text": "<audio controls src=\"/media/cc0-audio/t-rex-roar.mp3\">\n</audio>", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:20:34", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 12:20:34"}, {"file_name": "In the HTML form element, what does the method attribute do? What is the proper syntax for this attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the HTML form element, what does the method attribute do? What is the proper syntax for this attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In the HTML form element, what does the method attribute do? What is the proper syntax for this attribute? What values can you enter into the method attribute?", "answer_text": "<form action=\"/mailinglist.php\" method=\"POST\">...</form>\nThe method attribute specifies how the information should be sent to the server. There are two methods for sending this encoded data to the server: POST or GET.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:11:26", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:35:26"}, {"file_name": "Identify two to three socializing agents in your life and then explain how these socializing agents have informed your communication practices..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Identify two to three socializing agents in your life and then explain how these socializing agents have informed your communication practices.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[socializing agents]]"], "question_text": "Identify two to three socializing agents in your life and then explain how these socializing agents have informed your communication practices", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:17:19", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:41:19"}, {"file_name": "Are devices like Capitalism and The Free Market merely civil religions designed to regulate the population and prevent disorder?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Are devices like Capitalism and The Free Market merely civil religions designed to regulate the population and prevent disorder?.md", "type": "question", "subject": null, "related": ["[[Capitalism]]", "[[The Free Market]]", "[[civil religion]]", "[[Adam Smith]]"], "question_text": "Are devices like Capitalism and The Free Market merely civil religions designed to regulate the population and prevent disorder?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:08:29", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:32:29"}, {"file_name": "Ask the user to input two floating-point numbers. Calculates the sum, product, and average of these numbers. Rounds the results to 2 decimal places before printing them out...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Ask the user to input two floating-point numbers. Calculates the sum, product, and average of these numbers. Rounds the results to 2 decimal places before printing them out..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[float]]", "[[round()]]"], "question_text": "Ask the user to input two floating-point numbers. Calculates the sum, product, and average of these numbers. Rounds the results to 2 decimal places before printing them out.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:26:36", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:50:36"}, {"file_name": "What are the negative angle identities of sine and cosine?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are the negative angle identities of sine and cosine?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[sine]]", "[[cosine]]", "[[identity]]"], "question_text": "What are the negative angle identities of sine and cosine?", "answer_text": "sin(-\u03b8) = -sin(\u03b8)\ncos(-\u03b8) = cos(\u03b8)", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:11:46", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:35:46"}, {"file_name": "dictionary..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/dictionary.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[common argument pattern]]"], "question_text": "What are the common argument patterns?", "answer_text": "Modus Ponens\nModus Tollens\nHypothetical Syllogism", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:23:37", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:47:37"}, {"file_name": "What are the Specialized text-entry fields in a html input form element?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are the Specialized text-entry fields in a html input form element?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": null, "question_text": "What are the Specialized text-entry fields in a html input form element?", "answer_text": "<input type=\"password\">\n<input type=\"search\">\n<input type=\"email\">\n<input type=\"tel\">\n<input type=\"url\">\n<input type=\"radio\"> \n<input type=\"checkbox\"> \n<input type=\"file\">", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:35:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 12:35:49"}, {"file_name": "Given a string slice notation of . . ...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Given a string slice notation of . . ..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[slice notation]]"], "question_text": "Given a string slice notation of my_list[x:y:z]:\nAt what index does the z start at?", "answer_text": "The stride always starts at index x, if not specified it starts at index 0", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:29:08", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:53:08"}, {"file_name": "What do you always put after an if statement in python?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What do you always put after an if statement in python?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Python]]", "[[Syntax Error]]"], "question_text": "What do you always put after an if elif else statement in python?", "answer_text": ": <- A semicolon -> :", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:31:20", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:55:20"}, {"file_name": "How do you make a numbered list in an HTML document?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How do you make a numbered list in an HTML document?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "How do you make a numbered list in an HTML document?", "answer_text": "<ol>\n<li></li>\n<li></li>\n</ol>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:38:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:02:31"}, {"file_name": "When creating a table in html, how you use the colgroup and col elements?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When creating a table in html, how you use the colgroup and col elements?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]", "[[Accessibility]]"], "question_text": "When creating a table in html, how you use the colgroup and col elements?", "answer_text": "Make sure the colgroup has span/col elements totaling the number of columns. \nIf 5 columns then 5 col elements or 1 span2 and 3 col elements\n<table>\n<colgroup> </colgroup>\n<colgroup>\n<col class=\"example\">\n<col class=\"example2\">\n</colgroup>\n<tr></tr>\n<tr></tr>\n<tr></tr>\n<tr></tr>\n</table>\nMore info: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vU1yXsYjh3Y", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:33:09", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:57:09"}, {"file_name": "Which HTML element is used to specify a footer for a document or section?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Which HTML element is used to specify a footer for a document or section?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "Which HTML element is used to specify a footer for a document or section?", "answer_text": "<footer> </footer>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:29:29", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:53:29"}, {"file_name": "The angle of elevation to the top of a building in New York is found to be 9 degrees from the ground at a distance of 1 mile from the base of the building. Using this information, find the height of the building...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/The angle of elevation to the top of a building in New York is found to be 9 degrees from the ground at a distance of 1 mile from the base of the building. Using this information, find the height of the building..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[right triangle]]"], "question_text": "The angle of elevation to the top of a building in New York is found to be 9 degrees from the ground at a distance of 1 mile from the base of the building. Using this information, find the height of the building.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:36:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:00:31"}, {"file_name": "When creating a table in html, how do you create x amount of rows?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When creating a table in html, how do you create x amount of rows?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "When creating a table in html, how do you create a table with x amount of rows?", "answer_text": "Use x amount of <tr></tr> elements", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:39:45", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:03:45"}, {"file_name": "What are three arguments you can provide to a slice notation?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are three arguments you can provide to a slice notation?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[slice notation]]"], "question_text": "What are the three arguments you can provide in a slice notation method? given variable list1 = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]", "answer_text": "list1[start:end:stride]", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:32:11", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:56:11"}, {"file_name": "Given a circle, how would you find the area of a sector of it, given an angle?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Given a circle, how would you find the area of a sector of it, given an angle?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[area of a sector]]"], "question_text": "Given a circle, how would you find the area of a sector of it, given an angle?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:42:13", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:06:13"}, {"file_name": "Using slice notation and given variable, write two print statements that grab the first and last half of the string variable..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Using slice notation and given variable, write two print statements that grab the first and last half of the string variable.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[slice notation]]"], "question_text": "Using slice notation and given variable: usr_text, write two print statements that grab the first and last half of usr_text", "answer_text": "first_half = usr_text[:len(usr_text)//2]\nlast_half = usr_text[len(usr_text)//2:]\nprint(f'The first half of the string is \"{first_half}\"')\nprint(f'The second half of the string is \"{last_half}\"')", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:38:10", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:02:10"}, {"file_name": "A 23ft ladder leans up against a building so that the angle between the ground and the ladder is 73\u00b0. How high does the ladder reach up the building?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/A 23ft ladder leans up against a building so that the angle between the ground and the ladder is 73\u00b0. How high does the ladder reach up the building?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[right triangle]]"], "question_text": "A 23ft ladder leans up against a building so that the angle between the ground and the ladder is 73\u00b0. How high does the ladder reach up the building?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:31:14", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:55:14"}, {"file_name": "What is the formula for Area of sector?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the formula for Area of sector?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[radian]]", "[[area of a sector]]"], "question_text": "What is the formula for Area of sector?", "answer_text": "(1/2)*\u03b8*r^2", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:31:03", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:55:03"}, {"file_name": "Who is the Roman God of the Underworld?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Who is the Roman God of the Underworld?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mythology"], "related": ["[[Pluto]]"], "question_text": "Who is the Roman God of the Underworld", "answer_text": "Pluto", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:38:36", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:02:36"}, {"file_name": "In Algebra what does concave down refer to?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In Algebra what does concave down refer to?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": null, "question_text": "In Algebra what does concave down refer to?", "answer_text": "Look up graph in note:", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:38:22", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:02:22"}, {"file_name": "question about midline..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/question about midline.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[midline]]"], "question_text": "Given the function f(\u03b8) = 3cos(\u03b8)-4 \nWhat is the midline (y=?)", "answer_text": "-4", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:39:53", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:03:53"}, {"file_name": "What is meant by audience analysis?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is meant by audience analysis?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[audience]]"], "question_text": "What is meant by audience analysis?", "answer_text": "Strategies you use to get info about audience knowledge experience expectations and attitudes.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:28:20", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:52:20"}, {"file_name": "In the form element, what does the action attribute do? What is the proper syntax for this attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the form element, what does the action attribute do? What is the proper syntax for this attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In the HTML form element, what does the action attribute do? What is the proper syntax for this attribute?", "answer_text": "<form action=\"/mailinglist.php\" method=\"POST\">...</form>\n\nThe action attribute provides the location (URL) of the application or script that will be used to process the form. The action attribute in this example sends the data to a script called mailinglist.php", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:34:03", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 12:34:03"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML for inserting an image?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML for inserting an image?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML for inserting an image?", "answer_text": "<img src=\"image.gif\" alt=\"MyImage\">", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:27:03", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:51:03"}, {"file_name": "A 33-ft ladder leans against a building so that the angle between the ground and the ladder is 80\u00b0. How high does the ladder reach up the side of the building?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/A 33-ft ladder leans against a building so that the angle between the ground and the ladder is 80\u00b0. How high does the ladder reach up the side of the building?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[right triangle]]"], "question_text": "A 33-ft ladder leans against a building so that the angle between the ground and the ladder is 80\u00b0. How high does the ladder reach up the side of the building?", "answer_text": "sin(80) = H/33 \n33 * sin(80) = H", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:27:26", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:51:26"}, {"file_name": "When comparing characters in Python, the order of those characters is based on what?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When comparing characters in Python, the order of those characters is based on what?.md", "type": "question", "subject": null, "related": ["[[Unicode]]"], "question_text": "When comparing characters in Python, the order of those characters is based on what?", "answer_text": "The order of characters is based upon the unicode decimal value of that character.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:36:00", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:00:00"}, {"file_name": "In argument reconstruction, what is the argument itself defined as? In relation to it's components?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In argument reconstruction, what is the argument itself defined as? In relation to it's components?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Conclusion]]", "[[premise]]", "[[claim]]", "[[Evidence]]", "[[Reason]]"], "question_text": "In argument reconstruction, what is the argument itself defined as? In relation to it's components?", "answer_text": "The argument is the whole package of premises and conclusion(s). Much as an essay is to the words that comprise it.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:28:56", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:52:56"}, {"file_name": "How can you open a link a new tab browser window?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How can you open a link a new tab browser window?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "How can you open a link in a new tab/browser window in a <a> tag?", "answer_text": "<a href=URL target=\"_blank\">example.com</a>\nSpecifically target=\"_blank\"", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:28:36", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:52:36"}, {"file_name": "A right triangle is drawn with angle \u0251 opposite a side with length 33, angle \u03b8 oppsite a side with length 56, and hypotenuse 65. Find the sin and cosine of \u0251 and \u03b8..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/A right triangle is drawn with angle \u0251 opposite a side with length 33, angle \u03b8 oppsite a side with length 56, and hypotenuse 65. Find the sin and cosine of \u0251 and \u03b8.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": null, "question_text": "A right triangle is drawn with angle \u0251 opposite a side with length 33, angle \u03b8 oppsite a side with length 56, and hypotenuse 65. Find the sin and cosine of \u0251 and \u03b8", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:31:58", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:55:58"}, {"file_name": "When would you use the col (column) element?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When would you use the col (column) element?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "When would you use the col (column) element?", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:40:58", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:04:58"}, {"file_name": "How do you create an empty dictionary?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How do you create an empty dictionary?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[dictionary]]"], "question_text": "How do you create an empty dictionary? In Python?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:30:46", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:54:46"}, {"file_name": "Which approach detects if x is in the range -4 to +4?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Which approach detects if x is in the range -4 to +4?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[logical operator]]"], "question_text": "Which approach detects if x is in the range -4 to +4?\na) (x < -5) AND (x < 5)\nb) (x > -5) OR (x < 5)\nc) (x > -5) AND (x < 5)", "answer_text": "c) (x > -5) AND (x < 5)", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:27:41", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:51:41"}, {"file_name": "What would be an evolutionary advantage to cognitive biases?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What would be an evolutionary advantage to cognitive biases?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication", "psychology", "ecology"], "related": ["[[evolution]]"], "question_text": "What would be an evolutionary advantage to cognitive biases?", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:41:45", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 15:05:45"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?", "answer_text": "<br>\nNote: there is no closing tag for the <br> element", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:27:45", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:51:45"}, {"file_name": "What is the Sine of?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the Sine of?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[sine]]"], "question_text": "What is the sin of the following:\n0 - pi/6 - pi/4 - pi/3 - pi/2 - 2pi/3 - 3pi/4 - 5pi/6 - pi", "answer_text": "0 = 0\npi/6 = 1/2\npi/4 = sqrt(2)/2\npi/3 = sqrt(3)/2\npi/2 = 1\n2pi/3 = sqrt(3)/2\n3pi/4 = sqrt(2)/2\n5pi/6 = 1/2\npi = 0", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:29:52", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 14:53:52"}, {"file_name": "What are the three general types of audiences?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are the three general types of audiences?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[audience]]"], "question_text": "What are the three general types of audiences?", "answer_text": "Favorable Audience  \nUnfavorable Audience \nNeutral Audience", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:58:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:22:49"}, {"file_name": "Two kinds of freedom?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Two kinds of freedom?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Autonomy]]", "[[Freedom of Indifference]]"], "question_text": "Descartes makes a distinction between the \u201cFreedom of Indifference\u201d and a different, higher kind of Freedom. In class we called this higher kind \u201cAutonomy.\u201d Describe what is different between the two kinds of Freedom.", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:59:42", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:23:42"}, {"file_name": "Define Hypothetical syllogism..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Define Hypothetical syllogism.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Hypothetical syllogism]]"], "question_text": "What is the structure of a hypothetical syllogism argument?", "answer_text": "- If P then Q.- If Q then R.- Therefore, if P then R.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:54:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:18:31"}, {"file_name": "What do the thead, tfoot, and tbody html table elements do?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What do the thead, tfoot, and tbody html table elements do?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "What do the thead, tfoot, and tbody html table elements do?", "answer_text": "Group rows and columns / describes rows or groups of rows as belonging to a header, footer, or the body of a table.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:00:41", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:24:41"}, {"file_name": "In Python, what is the proper way to create a single element tuple?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In Python, what is the proper way to create a single element tuple?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Tuple]]"], "question_text": "In Python, what is the proper way to create a single element tuple?", "answer_text": "single_element_tuple = (42,)\nThe comma must be added to assign this as a single element tuple", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the stride argument in a string slice? What does it do?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the stride argument in a string slice? What does it do?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[slice notation]]"], "question_text": "What is the stride argument in a string slice? What does it do?\nUse my_str[0:10:x] as the example:", "answer_text": "`my_str[0:10:2]`\u00a0reads every other element between 0 and 10. The stride defaults to 1 if not specified.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:00:02", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:24:02"}, {"file_name": "What is the latin word for \"fire\"?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the latin word for \"fire\"?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication", "latin"], "related": ["[[igneous rock]]"], "question_text": "What is the latin word for \"fire\"?", "answer_text": "ignis", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the equation of a circle?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the equation of a circle?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Equation of a circle]]"], "question_text": "What is the equation of a circle?", "answer_text": "$$(x-h)^2 + (y-k)^2 = r^2$$", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:09:46", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 11:09:46"}, {"file_name": "Why are Uranus and Neptune so blue?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Why are Uranus and Neptune so blue?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["astronomy"], "related": null, "question_text": "Why are Uranus and Neptune so blue?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "The problem of evil is also referred to as?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/The problem of evil is also referred to as?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[theodicy]]"], "question_text": "The problem of evil is also referred to as?", "answer_text": "Theodicy", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:09:51", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:33:51"}, {"file_name": "Define Modus Ponens..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Define Modus Ponens.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Modus ponens]]"], "question_text": "Define the structure of a Modus Ponens argument", "answer_text": "- If P then Q.- P.- Therefore Q.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:02:07", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:26:07"}, {"file_name": "When creating a table in html, how do you create x amount of columns?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When creating a table in html, how do you create x amount of columns?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "When creating a table in html, how do you create a table x amount of columns?", "answer_text": "Make sure that every <tr></tr> element has x amount of <td></td> elements inside of it.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:59:21", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:23:21"}, {"file_name": "How do you make a checkbox in an HTML document?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How do you make a checkbox in an HTML document?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "How do you make a checkbox in an HTML document?", "answer_text": "<input type=\"checkbox\">", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:03:15", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:27:15"}, {"file_name": "What does the datalist element do? What is the proper html syntax for the datalist form element?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What does the datalist element do? What is the proper html syntax for the datalist form element?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "What does the datalist element do? What is the proper html syntax for the datalist form element?", "answer_text": "The datalist element allows the author to provide a drop-down menu of suggested values for any type of text input.\n<p> Education completed: <input type=\"text\" list=\"edulevel\" name=\"education\">\n<datalist id=\"edulevel\"> \n   <option value=\"HIgh School\">\n   <option value=\"Bachelors Degree\">\n   <option value=\"Masters Degree\">\n   <option value=\"PhD\">\n</datalist>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:52:42", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:16:42"}, {"file_name": "When using the input form element, if you don't include the type=\"\" attribute, what value does input default to?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When using the input form element, if you don't include the type=\"\" attribute, what value does input default to?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": null, "question_text": "When using the input form element, if you don't include the type=\"\" attribute, what value does input default to?", "answer_text": "<input name=\"\"> defaults to <input name=\"\" type=\"text\">", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "On a webpage you want your user to be able to enter more than one line of text for a form element, what element should you use?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/On a webpage you want your user to be able to enter more than one line of text for a form element, what element should you use?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "On a webpage you want your user to be able to enter more than one line of text for a form element, what element should you use?", "answer_text": "The <textarea> </textarea> element", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is a logical operator?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is a logical operator?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[circuits]]", "[[Operator]]", "[[logical operator]]", "[[Reserved words]]"], "question_text": "What is a logical operator?", "answer_text": "A logical operator treats operands as being True or False, and evaluates to True or False:\nOperators include: AND, OR, NOT", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the proper HTML markdown to add a list item text input form element?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the proper HTML markdown to add a list item text input form element?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "What is the proper HTML markdown to add a list item text input form element?", "answer_text": "<li>\n<label>Favorite color: <input type=\"text\" name=\"favcolor\" value=\"Red\" maxlength=\"50\">\n</label></li>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:57:29", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:21:29"}, {"file_name": "Convert a floating-point number provided by the user from scientific notation to its decimal equivalent. Then, converts it back to scientific notation using string formatting...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Convert a floating-point number provided by the user from scientific notation to its decimal equivalent. Then, converts it back to scientific notation using string formatting..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[float]]", "[[scientific notation]]"], "question_text": "Convert a floating-point number provided by the user from scientific notation to its decimal equivalent. Then, converts it back to scientific notation using string formatting.", "answer_text": "print(f\"{number:.2f}, {number:.2e}\")", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:02:32", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:26:32"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink to another website?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink to another website?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink to another website?", "answer_text": "<a href=\"http://www.example.com\">example.com</a>", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "If you want to disable controls to an HTML form, what attribute(s) might you use?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/If you want to disable controls to an HTML form, what attribute(s) might you use?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "If you want to disable controls to an HTML form, what attribute(s) might you use?", "answer_text": "the disabled or readonly attributes", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What context helps us understand Descartes\u2019 project of systematic doubt and his conclusion that both the mind and his knowledge are non-physical...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What context helps us understand Descartes\u2019 project of systematic doubt and his conclusion that both the mind and his knowledge are non-physical..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Rene Descartes]]", "[[scientific revolution]]"], "question_text": "What context helps us understand Descartes\u2019 project of systematic doubt and his conclusion that both the mind and his knowledge are non-physical.", "answer_text": "Hint: \"Safe for human beings\", consider what new ideas began to emerge during the scientific revolution.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:00:59", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:24:59"}, {"file_name": "What is Metaphysics? Define it, why is it important?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is Metaphysics? Define it, why is it important?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Metaphysics]]"], "question_text": "What is Metaphysics? Define it, why is it important?", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:57:37", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:21:37"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?", "answer_text": "<em>italics</em>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:53:10", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:17:10"}, {"file_name": "What are the several strategies to generate ideas?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are the several strategies to generate ideas?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["writing", "communication", "psychology"], "related": ["[[Brainstorm]]", "[[Clustering]]", "[[Freewriting]]", "[[Looping]]", "[[Questioning]]", "[[Drawing]]", "[[Outlining]]"], "question_text": "What are the several strategies to generate ideas?", "answer_text": "Brainstorming, Clustering, Freewriting, Looping, Questioning, Outlining, Drawing", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the domain of sine and cosine?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the domain of sine and cosine?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[sine]]", "[[cosine]]", "[[domain]]"], "question_text": "What is the domain of sine and cosine?", "answer_text": "(-\u221e,\u221e)", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:10:40", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:34:40"}, {"file_name": "What is the period of the function f(t) = sin((\u03c0 over 6 times t)..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the period of the function f(t) = sin((\u03c0 over 6 times t).md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[period]]"], "question_text": "What is the period of the function f(t) = sin((\u03c0/6)*t)", "answer_text": "P = 2\u03c0/B = 12", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "In argument reconstruction, what is a premise? How does this differ from a claim?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In argument reconstruction, what is a premise? How does this differ from a claim?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[premise]]", "[[claim]]"], "question_text": "In argument reconstruction, what is a premise? How does it differ from a claim?", "answer_text": "A premise is given as a reason in support of the truth of a Conclusion, a claim is a true/false statement.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:53:38", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:17:38"}, {"file_name": "Explain as clearly as possible Spinoza's two objections to the belief that human behavior is the result of the free will of the mind..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Explain as clearly as possible Spinoza's two objections to the belief that human behavior is the result of the free will of the mind.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Baruch Spinoza]]", "[[free will]]", "[[determinism]]"], "question_text": "Explain as clearly as possible Spinoza's two objections to the belief that human behavior is the result of the free will of the mind", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "In the input form element, what does the maxlength and minlength attributes do? What is the proper syntax for these attributes?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the input form element, what does the maxlength and minlength attributes do? What is the proper syntax for these attributes?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In the input form element, what does the maxlength and minlength attributes do? What is the proper syntax for these attributes?", "answer_text": "<maxlength =\"int\"> or <minlength=\"int\">\nsets a max length or minimum length to the amount of characters to be entered into an input field.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:01:53", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:25:53"}, {"file_name": "Given a string of length x, how would you get the last character in the string using slice notation?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Given a string of length x, how would you get the last character in the string using slice notation?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[slice notation]]"], "question_text": "Given a string of length x, how would you get the first all the way to the last character in the string using slice notation?", "answer_text": "variable[:end]", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:08:20", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:32:20"}, {"file_name": "How do you write an HTML comment?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How do you write an HTML comment?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "How do you write an HTML comment?", "answer_text": "<!-- Like this -->", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:59:28", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:23:28"}, {"file_name": "True or False, In HTML you can embed SVG . . ...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/True or False, In HTML you can embed SVG . . ..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "True or False, In HTML you can embed SVG elements directly into an HTML page", "answer_text": "True", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is meant by operator chaining in Python?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is meant by operator chaining in Python?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[operator chaining]]"], "question_text": "What is meant by operator chaining in Python?", "answer_text": "Python supports operator chaining. For example, a < b < c:", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:12:06", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:36:06"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML for inserting a background image?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML for inserting a background image?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML for inserting a background image?", "answer_text": "<body style=\"background-image:url(background.gif)\">", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Given a list, how do you sort it in ascending or descending order?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Given a list, how do you sort it in ascending or descending order?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[list]]", "[[sort()]]"], "question_text": "Given a list, how do you sort it in ascending or descending order?", "answer_text": "To sort in ascending order use:\nlist.sort()\nTo sort in descending order use:\nlist.sort(reverse = True)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:11:56", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 11:11:56"}, {"file_name": "Discuss and give examples of how changes in one area of worldview demands or inspires changes in other areas...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Discuss and give examples of how changes in one area of worldview demands or inspires changes in other areas..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[worldview]]", "[[Metaphysics]]", "[[Epistemology]]", "[[Moral Theory]]", "[[Political Theory]]"], "question_text": "Discuss and give examples of how changes in one area of worldview demands or inspires changes in other areas.", "answer_text": "This is an open ended question: Look up in the notes for details:", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:02:42", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:26:42"}, {"file_name": "When creating a table in html, how do you make an element span x amount of rows?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When creating a table in html, how do you make an element span x amount of rows?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "When creating a table in html, how do you make an element span x amount of rows?", "answer_text": "Use the rowspan=\"\" attribute\n<th rowspan=\"3\">example</th>\n<td rowspan=\"5\">example</td>\nrowspan takes an integer value", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:02:29", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 11:02:29"}, {"file_name": "What is Kant's comparison of \"Nonage\" to Intellectual Maturity?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is Kant's comparison of \"Nonage\" to Intellectual Maturity?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy", "history"], "related": ["[[Immanuel Kant]]", "[[Nonage]]"], "question_text": "What is Kant's comparison of \"Nonage\" to Intellectual Maturity?", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:58:44", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:22:44"}, {"file_name": "What is a relational operator?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is a relational operator?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Operator]]", "[[Relational Operator]]"], "question_text": "What is a relational operator?", "answer_text": "A relational operator checks how one operand's value relates to another, such as being greater than.\n<, >, <=, >=", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:02:59", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:26:59"}, {"file_name": "Why does audience matter in Public Speaking? or in what you Write?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Why does audience matter in Public Speaking? or in what you Write?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication", "writing"], "related": null, "question_text": "Why does audience matter in Public Speaking? or in what you Write?", "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:08:58", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:32:58"}, {"file_name": "Question transformations of sine and cosine..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Question transformations of sine and cosine.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[transformation]]"], "question_text": "Write the equation for sine and cosine, include the elements of transformation", "answer_text": "f(t) = Asin(Bt) + k\nf(t) = Acos(Bt) + k", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:12:56", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 11:12:56"}, {"file_name": "What is the negative identity of sin?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the negative identity of sin?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[sine]]"], "question_text": "What is the negative identity of sin?", "answer_text": "$$sin(-\\theta) = -sin(\\theta)$$", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:10:25", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:34:25"}, {"file_name": "What is the correct HTML element for adding a background color?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the correct HTML element for adding a background color?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the correct HTML element for adding a background color, inline?", "answer_text": "<body style=\"background-color:yellow;\">", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:53:05", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:17:05"}, {"file_name": "In HTML, all form control elements must include what attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In HTML, all form control elements must include what attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In HTML, all form control elements must include what attribute?", "answer_text": "All form control elements must include a name attribute so the form processing application can sort the information.", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:04:50", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:28:50"}, {"file_name": "What does Immanuel Kant mean by Nonage in his work \"What is Enlightenment?\"..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What does Immanuel Kant mean by Nonage in his work \"What is Enlightenment?\".md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy", "history"], "related": ["[[Immanuel Kant]]", "[[Enlightenment]]"], "question_text": "What does Immanuel Kant mean by Nonage in his work \"What is Enlightenment?\"", "answer_text": "\"Nonage is the inability to use one's own understanding without another's guidance.\"", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:05:19", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:29:19"}, {"file_name": "In the textarea form element, what does the rows attribute do? What is the proper syntax to use the rows attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the textarea form element, what does the rows attribute do? What is the proper syntax to use the rows attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In the textarea form element, what does the rows attribute do? What is the proper syntax to use the rows attribute?", "answer_text": "<textarea name=\"\" rows=\"5\"> </input>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:04:38", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:28:38"}, {"file_name": "When manipulating lists, you can use the insert method, what does it do? and How do you use it?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When manipulating lists, you can use the insert method, what does it do? and How do you use it?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[list]]"], "question_text": "When manipulating lists, you can use the insert method, what does it do? and How do you use it?", "answer_text": "fruits = [\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"] \nfruits.insert(1, \"orange\")  # Insert \"orange\" at index 1", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:11:22", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:35:22"}, {"file_name": "How does Spinoza define decision from the standpoint of thought, and how does he define it from the standpoint of extension?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How does Spinoza define decision from the standpoint of thought, and how does he define it from the standpoint of extension?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Baruch Spinoza]]"], "question_text": "How does Spinoza define decision from the standpoint of thought, and how does he define it from the standpoint of extension?", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:53:41", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:17:41"}, {"file_name": "When creating a table in html, how you make an element span x amount of columns?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When creating a table in html, how you make an element span x amount of columns?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]"], "question_text": "When creating a table in html, how you make an element span x amount of columns?", "answer_text": "use the colspan attribute:\n<th colspan=\"2\">example</th>\n<td colspan=\"3\">example</td>", "revision_streak": 2, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 11:10:05", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 13:34:05"}, {"file_name": "degrees to radians, sister question..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/degrees to radians, sister question.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[How to convert between radians and degrees?]]"], "question_text": "How do you convert from degrees to radians?", "answer_text": "1 degree = \u03c0/180, so multiple by (\u03c0/180)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "In what two ways do images appear on websites?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In what two ways do images appear on websites?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[img element]]"], "question_text": "In what two ways do images appear on websites?", "answer_text": "Either as in an inline element, or as a background image", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Write a relational expression using operator chaining - 02..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Write a relational expression using operator chaining - 02.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[operator chaining]]"], "question_text": "Write a relational expression using operator chaining:\nx is a nonnegative number less than 100\nif _______: True\nelse: False", "answer_text": "0 <= x < 100", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the HTML element for the largest heading?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the HTML element for the largest heading?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the HTML element for the largest heading?", "answer_text": "<h1>this is a heading</h1>", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "In the input form element, what does the value attribute do? What is the proper syntax for the value attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the input form element, what does the value attribute do? What is the proper syntax for the value attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In the input form element, what does the value attribute do? What is the proper syntax for the value attribute?", "answer_text": "The value attribute specifies default text that appears in the field when the form is loaded.\n<input name=\"\" value=\"default_text\". . .> </input>", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How do you create a new file using Python?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How do you create a new file using Python?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": null, "question_text": "How do you create a new file using Python?", "answer_text": "f = open(\"myfile.txt\", \"x\")", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Who coined the term theodicy?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Who coined the term theodicy?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy", "theology"], "related": ["[[theodicy]]"], "question_text": "Who coined the term theodicy? and When?", "answer_text": "Gottfried Leibniz coined the term in his book \"Theodicy\" in 1710", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Where did Martin Luther staple his Ninety Five Theses and when?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Where did Martin Luther staple his Ninety Five Theses and when?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["history"], "related": ["[[Martin Luther]]", "[[Protestant Reformation]]"], "question_text": "Where did Martin Luther staple his Ninety Five Theses and when?", "answer_text": "October 31, 1517 in Wittenburg, Germany", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Who was the ancient Greek God of opportunity and perfect timing?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Who was the ancient Greek God of opportunity and perfect timing?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mythology"], "related": ["[[kairos]]", "[[Ancient Greece]]"], "question_text": "Who was the ancient Greek God of opportunity and perfect timing?", "answer_text": "Kairos, or Caerus", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What are the accepted inputs to the scope attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are the accepted inputs to the scope attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Table Markup - 8]]", "[[Accessibility]]"], "question_text": "What are the accepted inputs to the scope attribute?", "answer_text": "<th scope=\"row\">\n<th scope=\"col\">\n<th scope=\"rowgroup\">\n<th scope=\"colgroup\">", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How do you put an ubuntu system to sleep using the CLI?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/How do you put an ubuntu system to sleep using the CLI?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Linux]]", "[[operating system]]"], "question_text": "How do you put an ubuntu system to sleep using the CLI?", "answer_text": "systemctl suspend", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the proper html syntax for an input type radio or checkbox field?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the proper html syntax for an input type radio or checkbox field?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "What is the proper html syntax for an input type radio or checkbox field?", "answer_text": "<form>\n   <fieldset>\n   <ol>\n   <li><input type=\"radio\" name=\"age\" value=\"value_here\"></li>\n   <!-- Value must be included -->\n   <li><input type=\"checkbox\" name=\"age\" value=\"value_here\"></li>\n   </ol>\n   </fieldset>\n<form>", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "In HTML, what does the name attribute do? and What is the proper syntax for the name attribute?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In HTML, what does the name attribute do? and What is the proper syntax for the name attribute?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In HTML, what does the name attribute do? and What is the proper syntax for the name attribute?", "answer_text": "<textarea name=\"comment\" . . .> . . . </textarea>\nThe name attribute provides the **variable** name for the form control. In this example, the text gathered by a textarea element is defined as the \"comment\" variable:", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the distance formula?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the distance formula?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Distance Formula]]"], "question_text": "What is the distance formula?", "answer_text": "sqrt( (x_2 - x_1)^2 + (y_2 - y_1)^2)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "In Python, how do you create a tuple variable..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In Python, how do you create a tuple variable.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Tuple]]", "[[Python]]"], "question_text": "In Python, how do you create a tuple variable?", "answer_text": "my_tuple = (1, \"hello\", 3.14)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Given a list with duplicate values, how do you find the total number of times a value appears in the list?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Given a list with duplicate values, how do you find the total number of times a value appears in the list?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[list]]"], "question_text": "Given a list with duplicate values, how do you find the total number of times a value appears in the list?", "answer_text": "with the count method: See the example below\ncolors = [\"red\", \"blue\", \"green\", \"blue\"] \nprint(colors.count(\"blue\"))  # Output: 2\nstring1=\"Hello\"\nprint(string1.count(\"l\"))", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What character is used to indicate an end tag in an HTML element?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What character is used to indicate an end tag in an HTML element?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What character is used to indicate an end tag in an HTML element? Provide an example.", "answer_text": "/ as in </a> or </em> or </body>", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the U+ code for Greek Letter Theta?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the U+ code for Greek Letter Theta?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[Unicode hexidecimal table]]"], "question_text": "What is the U+ code for Greek Letter Theta?", "answer_text": "U+03B8", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "When did the protestant reformation start?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When did the protestant reformation start?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["history", "religion"], "related": ["[[Protestant Reformation|Reformation]]"], "question_text": "When did the protestant reformation start? What event is known to be the starting point?", "answer_text": "Martin Luther, Ninety-five Theses, Wittenberg Germany on October 31, 1517", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "In the input form element, what does the size attribute default to?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In the input form element, what does the size attribute default to?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[Learning Web Design - Forms - 9]]"], "question_text": "In the input form element, what does the size attribute default to?", "answer_text": "20 characters", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Write a relational expression using operator chaining - 01..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Write a relational expression using operator chaining - 01.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": ["[[operator chaining]]"], "question_text": "Write a relational expression using operator chaining: \nx is less than y but greater than z.", "answer_text": "z < x < y", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is the DOCTYPE format for HTML5?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the DOCTYPE format for HTML5?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["web_design"], "related": ["[[HTML]]"], "question_text": "What is the DOCTYPE format for HTML5?", "answer_text": "<!DOCTYPE html>", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "question_template..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/templates/question_template.md", "type": "question", "subject": null, "related": null, "question_text": null, "answer_text": null, "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How do you reconstruct arguments?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/How do you reconstruct arguments?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy", "communication"], "related": ["[[argument]]", "[[Reconstructing Arguments - Kareem Khalifa]]"], "question_text": "How do you reconstruct arguments?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How to convert between radians and degrees?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/How to convert between radians and degrees?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": null, "question_text": "How to convert from radians and degrees?", "answer_text": "1 radian = 180/\u03c0, so multiply radians by 180 and divide by \u03c0.", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How do you determine if a relevant expert would disagree with a premise?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/How do you determine if a relevant expert would disagree with a premise?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[premise]]", "[[argument]]"], "question_text": "How do you determine if a relevant expert would disagree with a premise?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is a universal, in regards to an argument?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/What is a universal, in regards to an argument?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[argument]]"], "question_text": "What is a universal, in regards to an argument?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Sketch a graph of $$(x-2)^2 + (y+3)^2 = 9$$..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/Sketch a graph of $$(x-2)^2 + (y+3)^2 = 9$$.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["None"], "question_text": "Sketch a graph of $$(x-2)^2 + (y+3)^2 = 9$$", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Why should you reconstruct arguments?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/Why should you reconstruct arguments?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy", "communication"], "related": ["[[argument]]"], "question_text": "Why should you reconstruct arguments?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "In the discrimination court case described by Crenshaw in the video, which intersectional identities were highlighted as the focus of the argument?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/In the discrimination court case described by Crenshaw in the video, which intersectional identities were highlighted as the focus of the argument?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["None"], "question_text": "In the discrimination court case described by Crenshaw in the video, which intersectional identities were highlighted as the focus of the argument?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Find the distance between points (1,6) and (3, -5)..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/Find the distance between points (1,6) and (3, -5).md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Distance Formula]]"], "question_text": "Find the distance between points (1,6) and (3, -5)", "answer_text": "sqrt(125)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How could rhetoric - the art and practice of persuasion - act as a counter to war?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/How could rhetoric - the art and practice of persuasion - act as a counter to war?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["writing", "english"], "related": ["None"], "question_text": "How could rhetoric - the art and practice of persuasion - act as a counter to war?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How can a speaker be effective in teaching or persuading an audience?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/How can a speaker be effective in teaching or persuading an audience?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Rhetoric]]", "[[public speaking]]"], "question_text": "How can a speaker be effective in teaching or persuading an audience?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How, exactly, does one read for enlightenment?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/How, exactly, does one read for enlightenment?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[Enlightenment]]"], "question_text": "How, exactly, does one read for enlightenment?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How do we determine what a faithful interpretation of an argument is?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/How do we determine what a faithful interpretation of an argument is?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[argument]]"], "question_text": "How do we determine what a faithful interpretation of an argument is?", "answer_text": "1. call any interpretation of an argument that accurately represents an author's intended meaning a faithful interpretation of that argument. \n2. judge faithfulness by how well it accord with textual evidence,", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Think of a time when you have been moved to change your thinking about a topic . . ...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/Think of a time when you have been moved to change your thinking about a topic . . ..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[public speaking]]"], "question_text": "Think of a time when you have been moved to change your thinking about a topic. Maybe it was hearing about child labor in sweatshops that produce products from your favorite store, or learning about racial segregation in school districts, or becoming educated about the tons of food that goes to waste across the country each year. In the following response, write 3\u20134 thoughtful and detailed sentences about what moved you to change your thinking or position on a topic. Was the message delivered in-person or mediated? What was in the content of the message that you found moving? Who sent the message? What about the messenger made you not only listen, but be moved to change? In general, are you someone who is more motivated to change because you have had an emotional response, logical one, or a combination of both?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What constitutes public speaking in our contemporary, diverse world?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/What constitutes public speaking in our contemporary, diverse world?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": null, "question_text": "What constitutes public speaking in our contemporary, diverse world?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Why should mankind's destiny rely on such intellectual progress? On Enlightenment?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/Why should mankind's destiny rely on such intellectual progress? On Enlightenment?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": "", "question_text": "Why should mankind's destiny rely on such intellectual progress? On Enlightenment?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How do we achieve a true reform of modes of thought?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/How do we achieve a true reform of modes of thought?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": "", "question_text": "How do we achieve a true reform of modes of thought?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What makes something memorable?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/What makes something memorable?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["writing", "psychology"], "related": ["None"], "question_text": "What makes something memorable?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What are some methods that speaker might deploy to effectively teach or persuade an audience?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/What are some methods that speaker might deploy to effectively teach or persuade an audience?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Rhetoric]]", "[[public speaking]]"], "question_text": "What are some methods that speaker might deploy to effectively teach or persuade an audience?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What are the common argument patterns?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/What are the common argument patterns?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[common argument pattern]]"], "question_text": "What are the common argument patterns?", "answer_text": "Modus Ponens\nModus Tollens \nHypothetical Syllogism\nDisjunctive Syllogism", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "How do maintain order, while also constantly updating our social and spiritual customs based on new \"enlightenment\"?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/How do maintain order, while also constantly updating our social and spiritual customs based on new \"enlightenment\"?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": "", "question_text": "How do maintain order, while also constantly updating our social and spiritual customs based on new \"enlightenment\"?", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "Write an equation for a circle centered at the point (-3, 2) with radius 4..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/Write an equation for a circle centered at the point (-3, 2) with radius 4.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Equation of a circle]]"], "question_text": "Write an equation for a circle centered at the point (-3, 2) with radius 4", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-18 21:09:31", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-19 21:09:31"}, {"file_name": "What is tangent defined as in terms of y-x and sine-cosine?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is tangent defined as in terms of y-x and sine-cosine?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 5.4 The Other Trigonometric Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is tangent defined as in terms of y-x and sine-cosine?", "answer_text": "(y / x) OR ( sin(\u03b8) / cos(\u03b8) )", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 07:06:44", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 07:06:44"}, {"file_name": "What is the period of the tangent function m(\u03b8) = tan(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the period of the tangent function m(\u03b8) = tan(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the period of the tangent function m(\u03b8) = tan(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "\u03c0", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 07:06:44", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 07:06:44"}, {"file_name": "What is the cofunction identity of cos(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the cofunction identity of cos(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 5.5 Right Triangle Trigonometry]]"], "question_text": "What is the cofunction identity of cos(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "cos(\u03b8) = sin( (\u03c0/2) - \u03b8)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the process of sketching a graph of secant or cosecant?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the process of sketching a graph of secant or cosecant?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": null, "question_text": "What is the process of sketching a graph of secant or cosecant?", "answer_text": "First sketch out a graph of the equivalent cos/sin function.\n\ndraw vertical asymptotes at the interval of the period, starting at the origin + 1/2 * period. (if period is 2\u03c0 then an asymptote will be at intervals of 2\u03c0 started at -\u03c0 and \u03c0 accordingly.)\n\ndraw parabolic x^2 function originating from each peak or valley", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the reciprocal identity of sec(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the reciprocal identity of sec(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the reciprocal identity of sec(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "1 / cos(\u03b8)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the cofunction identity of sin(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the cofunction identity of sin(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 5.5 Right Triangle Trigonometry]]"], "question_text": "What is the cofunction identity of sin(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "sin(\u03b8) = cos( (\u03c0/2) - \u03b8)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the negative identity of cot(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the negative identity of cot(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the negative identity of cot(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "cot(-\u03b8) = -cot(\u03b8)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the unicode U+ code for the \u2260 symbol?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the unicode U+ code for the \u2260 symbol?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Unicode hexidecimal table]]"], "question_text": "What is the unicode U+ code for the \u2260 symbol?", "answer_text": "U+2260 -> \u2260", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "Is cos(\u03b8) even or odd?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Is cos(\u03b8) even or odd?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.1 Sinusoidal Graphs]]"], "question_text": "Is cos(\u03b8) even or odd?", "answer_text": "Even function", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "Prove that tan(\u03b8) = -cot(\u03b8 - pi over 2)..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Prove that tan(\u03b8) = -cot(\u03b8 - pi over 2).md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "Prove that tan(\u03b8) = -cot(\u03b8 - (\u03c0/2) )", "answer_text": "Start on the left side of the equation:\nAnswer won't be given here, look up example 6.2.3 in the referenced text\nHint: negative and confunction identities are required to solve this", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "Sketch a graph of f(\u03b8) = 3tan( (\u03c0-6) \u03b8..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Sketch a graph of f(\u03b8) = 3tan( (\u03c0-6) \u03b8.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "Sketch a graph of f(\u03b8) = 3tan( (\u03c0/6) * \u03b8)", "answer_text": "3 adjusts the amplitude.\npi/6 -> period = 6", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the domain of cot(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the domain of cot(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the domain of cot(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "\u03b8 \u2260 k\u03c0, where k is an integer", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the range of tan(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the range of tan(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the range of tan(\u03b8)? Describe and provide interval notation.", "answer_text": "The range of the tan(\u03b8) function is all real numbers,\n(-\u221e, \u221e)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the negative identity of sec(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the negative identity of sec(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the negative identity of sec(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "sec(-\u03b8) = sec(\u03b8)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "Describe the graph behavior of the sec(\u03b8) function..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Describe the graph behavior of the sec(\u03b8) function.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "Describe the graph behavior of the sec(\u03b8) function", "answer_text": "We end up with parabolas originating from the peak and valley of where the equivalent cos(\u03b8) function. Where the cos(\u03b8) part is not covered.", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the range of cot(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the range of cot(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the range of cot(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "(-\u221e,\u221e)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "Verify the negative angle identity of tan(\u03b8) using the negative values of sin and cosine..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Verify the negative angle identity of tan(\u03b8) using the negative values of sin and cosine.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "Use the negative identity of  sin/cos to verify the negative angle identity of tan(\u03b8).\ntan(-\u03b8) = ( sin(-\u03b8) / cos(-\u03b8) )", "answer_text": "( -sin(\u03b8) / cos(\u03b8) ) = - tan(\u03b8)\nsince sin/cos = tan -> move the - to the edge of the equation.", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "When is tan(\u03b8) undefined?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When is tan(\u03b8) undefined?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "When is tan(\u03b8) undefined?", "answer_text": "When cos(\u03b8) = 0", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the domain of tan(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the domain of tan(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the domain of tan(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "The domain of tan(\u03b8) is:\n\u03b8 \u2260 ( \u03c0/2 ) + k\u03c0, where k is an integer", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the range of the secant and cosecant functions?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the range of the secant and cosecant functions?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the range of the secant and cosecant functions?", "answer_text": "(-\u221e,-1] \u22c3 [1, \u221e)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "Is sin(\u03b8) even or odd?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Is sin(\u03b8) even or odd?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "Is sin(\u03b8) even or odd?", "answer_text": "Odd function", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the negative identity of tan(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the negative identity of tan(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the negative identity of tan(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "tan(-\u03b8) = -tan(\u03b8)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the period of sec(\u03b8) and csc(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the period of sec(\u03b8) and csc(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the period of sec(\u03b8) and csc(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "2\u03c0", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the unicode u+ code for the \u22c3 symbol? big cup or union..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the unicode u+ code for the \u22c3 symbol? big cup or union.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["computer_science"], "related": null, "question_text": "What is the unicode u+ code for the \u22c3 symbol? big cup or union", "answer_text": "U+22c3 -> \u22c3", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "Sketch a graph of csc. . ...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/Sketch a graph of csc. . ..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "Sketch a graph of 2csc( (\u03c0/2)*\u03b8) + 1", "answer_text": "Plot into desmos, interface does not support images", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "When is the graph of cotangent undefined?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When is the graph of cotangent undefined?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "When is the graph of cotangent undefined?", "answer_text": "when the sine = 0 \nat 0, \u03c0, 2\u03c0, etc.", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "When is the function sec(\u03b8) undefined?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When is the function sec(\u03b8) undefined?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "When is the function sec(\u03b8) undefined?", "answer_text": "When cos(\u03b8) = 0  \nHint: recall the reciprocal identity of sec(\u03b8)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the negative identity of csc(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the negative identity of csc(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the negative identity of csc(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "csc(-\u03b8) = -csc(\u03b8)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the domain of csc(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the domain of csc(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the domain of csc(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "\u03b8 \u2260 k\u03c0", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the domain of sec(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the domain of sec(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the domain of sec(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "\u03b8 \u2260(\u03c0/2) + k\u03c0", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What is the period of cot(\u03b8)?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the period of cot(\u03b8)?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["mathematics"], "related": ["[[Lippman_Trig_Text Section 6.2 Graphs of the Other Trig Functions]]"], "question_text": "What is the period of cot(\u03b8)?", "answer_text": "\u03c0", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 11:58:16", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 11:58:16"}, {"file_name": "What are the common argument patternss?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/University of Montana - Education/Classes/What are the common argument patternss?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["philosophy"], "related": ["[[common argument pattern]]"], "question_text": "What are the common argument patterns?", "answer_text": "Modus Ponens\nModus Tollens \nHypothetical Syllogism\nDisjunctive Syllogism", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-19 12:42:19", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-20 12:42:19"}, {"file_name": "What are five broad categories of informative speaking?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are five broad categories of informative speaking?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[informative speaking]]"], "question_text": "What are five broad categories of informative speaking?", "answer_text": "People, Objects, Events, Processes, or Ideas", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "What are strategies for speaking where difficult language makes an idea hard for your audience to understand? How do you effectively overcome this barrier?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are strategies for speaking where difficult language makes an idea hard for your audience to understand? How do you effectively overcome this barrier?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Difficult language]]"], "question_text": "What are strategies for speaking where difficult language makes an idea hard for your audience to understand? How do you effectively overcome this barrier? explain four things you can do:", "answer_text": "1. Provide a common exemplar, or an ideal example of the concept.\n2. Provide a definition that explains the essential characteristics of the concept.\n3. Share several examples and nonexamples of the concept to help distinguish between what the concept is and what it is not.\n4. Give your audience an opportunity to practice identifying examples and non examples of the concept. (Participation)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "When did Immanuel Kant write What is Enlightenment?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When did Immanuel Kant write What is Enlightenment?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["history"], "related": ["[[What is Enlightenment? - Immanuel Kant]]"], "question_text": "When did Immanuel Kant write What is Enlightenment?", "answer_text": "1784", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "What does the CRAAP Test stand for when evaluating a source?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What does the CRAAP Test stand for when evaluating a source?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[CRAAP Test]]"], "question_text": "What does the CRAAP Test stand for when evaluating a source?", "answer_text": "Currency \nRelevance\nAuthority\nAccuracy\nPurpose", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "What is the difference between a denotative definition and a connotative definition?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the difference between a denotative definition and a connotative definition?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Definition]]", "[[Connotative definition]]", "[[Denotative definition]]"], "question_text": "What is the difference between a denotative definition and a connotative definition?", "answer_text": "The denotative definition is the dictionary definition, or the literal definition that explains how the word is used in formal contexts. The connotative definition of a word includes an explanation of how the word is used in contemporary contexts, informal or colloquial talk, along with emotional responses attached to the word.", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "What are the three primary reasons that ideas can be difficult to understand?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are the three primary reasons that ideas can be difficult to understand?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Difficult language]]", "[[Difficult to believe]]", "[[Difficult to picture]]"], "question_text": "What are the three primary reasons that ideas can be difficult to understand?", "answer_text": "1. Difficult Language (the language or concepts are difficult)\n2. Difficult to Picture (the structure or process is hard to envision)\n3. Difficult to believe (the idea is difficult to believe)", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "What is the key difference between explaining and informing?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What is the key difference between explaining and informing?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Explain]]", "[[Inform]]"], "question_text": "What is the key difference between explaining and informing?", "answer_text": "When we inform, we are making the audience aware of a phenomenon, whereas when we explain an idea, we deepen the audience\u2019s understanding of that phenomenon (Rowan, 2003).", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "What are four steps to take when speaking on an idea that is difficult to believe?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are four steps to take when speaking on an idea that is difficult to believe?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Difficult to believe]]"], "question_text": "What are four steps to take when speaking on an idea that is difficult to believe?", "answer_text": "1. Acknowledge - your audiences everyday undestanding, or \"lay\" theory, of how the phenomenon works. Consider asking your audience to describe the concept in their own words to better understand their perspective\n2. Acknowledge - Why that explanation seems plausible on the surface\n3. Explain - why that impression is incorrect or incomplete, show examples that demonstrate why it is not adequate.\n4. Explain - the concept or theory more completely and illustrate why it is effective.", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "When we explain something, what should we focus on?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/When we explain something, what should we focus on?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Explain]]"], "question_text": "When we explain something, what should we focus on?", "answer_text": "The HOW and WHY of the topic.", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "What are two strategies for explaining an idea that is difficult to picture?..md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/What are two strategies for explaining an idea that is difficult to picture?.md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": null, "question_text": "What are two strategies for explaining an idea that is difficult to picture?", "answer_text": "1. The use of visual graphics: such as diagrams, models, simplified drawings, or cartoon illustrations.\n2. Verbal organizational cues: help to understand the relationship among the parts or processes as you give an explanation.\n3. Use of metaphors or analogies", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}, {"file_name": "In a public speech - Name the six core explanatory strategies for helping an audience understand a concept...md", "file_path": "/home/karibar/Documents/Education/Un-Sorted/In a public speech - Name the six core explanatory strategies for helping an audience understand a concept..md", "type": "question", "subject": ["communication"], "related": ["[[Definition]]", "[[Humor]]", "[[Rewards]]", "[[Participation]]", "[[signposts]]"], "question_text": "In a public speech - Name the six core explanatory strategies for helping an audience understand a concept.", "answer_text": "1. Clear definitions\n2. Use of Humor\n3. Use of Rewards Intrinsic and Extrinsic\n4. Audience Participation\n5. Signposts and Repetition \n6. Use all of the senses", "revision_streak": 1, "last_revised": "2024-02-20 10:50:49", "next_revision_due": "2024-02-21 10:50:49"}]